100% medically INaccurate.
The Human Centipede 2 (Full Sequence) is a drama,
horror, crime film directed by Tom Six.
Inspired by the fictional Dr.
Heiter, disturbed loner Martin dreams of creating a 12-person
centipede and sets out to realize his sick fantasy.
Martin, played by Laurence R. Harvey.
Miss Yennie, played by Ashlynn Yennie.
Paul, played by Dominic Borrelli.
Valerie, played by Georgia Goodrick.
Candy, played by Maddi Black.
Karrie, played by Kandace Caine.
The Human Centipede 2 (Full Sequence) is a 2011 psychological body
horror film written, directed, and co-produced by Tom Six.
An international co-production of the Netherlands and the United Kingdom, and the sequel to
Six's 2009 film The Human Centipede (First Sequence), the film stars Laurence R.
Harvey as a psychiatrically and intellectually impaired English man who watches and becomes obsessed with the first Human Centipede film, and decides to make his own "centipede"
consisting of 12 people by using crude and violent techniques to connect their lips to each others buttocks, including Ashlynn Yennie, an actress from the first film.
The Human Centipede 2 (Full Sequence) received substantial attention and controversy for its graphic
depictions of violence, sexual violence, forced defecation, and overall body horror.
It was subject to heavy censorship throughout the world where it was sometimes
edited to remove objectionable content or banned altogether.
It was critically panned, with much criticism focused on its acting, plot, editing, and
violence, although Harvey's performance received some praise from critics.
The film explores themes of child abuse, baby, rape, insect, sexual obsession.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.